Mss.Ms.Coll.104
American Philosophical Society
- Series II. Correspondence-Hare Family, 1724-1965
  - Newspaper articles - New York Times Magazine, 1927 January 2; No. 2955
    "Dog Sled Driving Grows as a Sport" and "America Amazed Visitors Even in 1837".
  - Owen Wister to Mrs. Hare, 1927 January 5; No. 2956
    Thank you for invitation to come next Sunday.
  - Musicale program, 1927 January 9; No. 2957
    "Harford", Radnor, Pennsylvania.
  - Gregor to Mrs. Hare, 1927 January 10; No. 2958
    Thank you for gifts - pen and book.
  - Willing to Mrs. H.B. Hare, 1927 January 11; No. 2959
    In reference to financing schooling for Oliver Perry Smith, Jr.
  - Medications, 1927; No. 2960
    One from doctor in Aix les Bains. Treatment of toe. For bronchial cough.
  - Cass to Mrs. Hare, 1927 January 26; No. 2961
    Family's illnesses. Could I spend night with you when I go to Mary Strong's funeral?
  - Molly Coles to Mrs. Hare, 1927 January 29; No. 2962
    Enjoyed your note after my fall.
  - Truxtun to Mrs. Horace B. Hare, 1927 February 14; No. 2963
    Had Dance. Glad Katharine got away safely and that Mother took the trip south.
  - O.P. Smith to Mrs. Emily P. Hare, 1927 February 19; No. 2964
    Thank you for check. Doctor left dirt in my wound. Competing in Vermont for American Olympic Team Ski jumping. Sorry Willing has lumbago.
  - Pictures, postcards, photos and printed articles, 1927 March 1; No. 2965
    On Charleston, S.C. (particularly Middleton Place Gardens).
  - Truxtun to Mrs. Horace B. Hare, 1927 March 17; No. 2966
    Weather. Coming home next week.
  - O.P. Smith to Mrs. Emily P. Hare, 1927 April 7; No. 2967
    Thank you for things you sent to Agnes. More trouble with my head. Expect to go to Europe or New England for a year's visit.
  - Katharine Hare, Jr. to Mrs. Horace Binney Hare, 1927 April 8; No. 2968
    Love it here. Gondolas.
  - C.W. Beale to Mrs. Horace B. Hare, 1927 April 8; No. 2969
    Maria very ill.
  - Beckie Spencer to Mrs. Horace Binney Hare, 1927 April 22; No. 2970
    Sorry not to have seen you. Appreciate your remembrance.
  - Cass to Mrs. Hare, 1927 April 22; No. 2971
    My illness - nurses, attentions, etc. Family. Reading. Friendly correspondence.
  - Katharine to Nanna, 1927 May 2; No. 2972
  - C.W. Beale to Mrs. Horace B. Hare, 1927 May 4; No. 2973
    Constance in Philadelphia. Interested to hear Horace and wife going to recently acquired Chateau in France. On Oliver, Commodore Truxton, Granny, Grandfather Beale, Uncle Edward and Spanish friend from Ecuador. On "answering our own prayers" (subconcious).
  - Horace to Mrs. Horace B. Hare, 1927 May 6; No. 2974
    Will land tomorrow - smooth voyage. The baby and Cardinal Dougherty and others on board.
  - E.M. Hare to C. Willing Hare, 1927 May 6; No. 2975
    Thank you for all you did to get us off. Baby's doll admired by all the children on board. Nice servants - even good to the dogs.
  - Ellen Mary Hare to Mrs. Horace Binney Hare, 1927 May 6; No. 2976
    Thank you for grapes and fruit - baby drinking orange juice. Ellen Mary a peerless sailor and owing to her we met most of the passengers - she especially attracted Cardinal Dougherty.
  - Cass to Mrs. Horace Binney Hare, 1927 May 10; No. 2977
    Poetic letter and one in French, and poem "The Censer".
  - Horace to Mrs. Horace B. Hare, 1927 May 12; No. 2978
    Landing and our arrival at Beaufresne. Household staff. The house (nearly 400 yrs. old) and the grounds.
  - Dr. Thomas F. Branson to Mrs. Horace B. Hare, 1927 May 23; No. 2979
    Diet.
  - Horace to Mrs. Horace Binney Hare, 1927 May 26; No. 2980
    Written by Ellen to give you a true picture of life here.
  - Ellen Mary Hare to Miss Esther Hare, 1927 May; No. 2981
    Saw doctor for baby - not needed but comfort to know. Katharine coming. Tragic about Ingersoll baby.
  - Ellen Mary and Horace Hare to C. Willing Hare, 1927 May 27; No. 2982
    About pictures and activities of Ellen Mary. So many things to do to house. Cost of labor. Saw Katharine.
  - Horace to Miss Esther Hare, 1927 May 28; No. 2983
    Delighted to hear you are coming over with the Hutchinsons. Quiet here. Katharine is with us - she met Lindbergh. About stone not being delivered. The baby well.
  - Esther to Mrs. H.B. Hare, 1927 June 5; No. 2984
    Bon voyage gifts. Boat nice. Shall miss you.
  - Esther to Mrs. Horace B. Hare, 1927 June 8; No. 2985
    Very comfortable ship - companions, cabin, decks, etc.
  - Horace to Miss Esther Hare, 1927 June 10; No. 2986
    Katharine Jr. is with us. I am going to town to see Katharine and might go over to London.
  - Esther to C. Willing Hare, 1927 June 14; No. 2987
    Comfortable crossing. All about the ship. Thanks for all you did in sending me off.
  - Meta H. Hutchinson to Mrs. Horace Hare, 1927 June 12; No. 2988
    Esther well and we're looking forward to our trip in England.
  - Esther to Mrs. H.B. Hare, 1927 June 12; No. 2989
    Voyage about over - been very comfortable. Electric stoves.
  - Esther to Mrs. H.B. Hare, 1927 June 14; No. 2990
    Description of activities here. Going to Oxford.
  - Cass to Mrs. Hare, 1927 June 16; No. 2991
    Rosemary's accident - watching Lindbergh, stepped backward and fell down iron stairs.
  - Esther to Mrs. H.B. Hare, 1927 June 17; No. 2992
    Here for tea. Seeing lovely villages.
  - Esther to Mrs. H.B. Hare, 1927 June 17; No. 2993
    General travel correspondence. Motored out to K's place.
  - Katharine to Mrs. Horace B. Hare, 1927 June 18; No. 2994
    K. Jr. joined us after being with Horace and Ellen. We visited them for a day at Beaufresne.
  - Esther to Mrs. H.B. Hare, 1927 June 19; No. 2995
    Travels and sights - Christ Church, colleges, visit to Lady Osler's and Mrs. Rathbone's motor trip, Bath and other villages, etc.
  - Katharine and Patty to Miss Esther Hare, 1927 June 20; No. 2996
    Excited over seeing Mother. Dress from Worth's. Thank you for check. Sights. Visited Uncle Harry and Ellen Mary and baby. Opera - Romeo and Juliet.
  - Esther to Mrs. H.B. Hare, 1927 June 22; No. 2997
    Program of Royal visit to Regent St. and University College.
  - Esther to Mrs. H.B. Hare, 1927 June 24; No. 2998
    Travels, sights and friends.
  - Esther to Mrs. H.B. Hare, 1927 June 24; No. 2999
    Social activities here.
  - Page of English newspaper - The Times, 1927 June 25; No. 3000
    Pictures of "Shakespeare in an Oxford Garden and Men's Doubles at Wimbledon", etc.
  - Horace to Miss Esther Hare, 1927 June 23; No. 3000a
    Could not go to London now - will see you in Paris. (Hotel bill - Symond's)
  - Katharine to Miss Esther Hare, 1927 June 25; No. 3001
    Welcome to Paris - sorry I cannot see you tomorrow.
  - Esther to Mrs. H.B. Hare, 1927 June 27; No. 3002
    Saw Nancy. Horace and Ellen came, and K., K. Jr. and Patty. Sights in England.
  - Horace to Miss Esther Hare, 1927 June 28; No. 3003
    Invitation to come visit us.
  - Esther to Mrs. H.B. Hare, 1927 July 2; No. 3004
    Very comfortable at hotel. Shopping and sights. Day at Beaufresne and the baby and Patty. Am going down to stay at Beaufresne. Luches, dinners, teas, etc.
  - Miss Esther Hare, 1927 July; No. 3005
    Bills from European trip.
  - Horace to C. Willing Hare, 1927 July 5; No. 3006
    Have hedge cut. Would love to have you and Mother.
  - C.W. Beale to Mrs. Horace B. Hare, 1927 July 5; No. 3007
    General witty correspondence.
  - Cass to Mrs. Hare, 1927 July 5; No. 3008
    Daily with Rosemary who is recuperating from accident. On the rich and poor in cities. Capes.
  - Cass to Mrs. Hare, 1927 July 11; No. 3009
    Rosemary's bone is healing. I love to be needed. Molly's tonsilitis. Little Church 'Round the Corner.
  - Horace to Mrs. Horace B. Hare, 1927 July 12; No. 3010
    Esther with us. All well. Pictures enclosed of baby, house, geese and dog.
  - Esther to Mrs. H.B. Hare, 1927 July 12; No. 3011
    Activities here - sights, walking, church, motoring, etc. The baby and the chateau.
  - C.W. Beale to Mrs. Horace B. Hare, 1927 July 14; No. 3012
    Thank you for dressing gown. Remember when I walked 42 miles.
  - Cass to Mrs. Hare, 1927 July 14; No. 3013
    To say Rosemary adores you and your baby blue pillow.
  - Mother to Miss E.B. Hare, 1927 July 15; No. 3014
    I have been writing so you must not be receiving my mail.
  - Mother to Miss Esther Hare, 1927 July 16; No. 3015
    Going to Maine - everyone else going to Europe. Had dinner party for Mrs. Cassatt. Ned fell out of pony cart and broke his arm.
  - Mother to Miss Esther Hare, 1927 July 17; No. 3016
    Truxtun Jr. has gone to camp. About Peter. Mr. Gurley coming for supper. Going to Bar Harbor - Willing thinks he can travel with me on his way to the woods.
  - Molly Baltz to Mrs. Horace Hare, 1927 July 18; No. 3017
    To thank you for Rosemary's pillow and flowers.
  - Esther to Mrs. H.B. Hare, 1927 July 20; No. 3018
    Trying to change passage to an earlier date. Pleasant here with Horace, Ellen and the baby who is a constant joy to all. Going to Paris again and may return here with Margaretta. Joyful Truxtun Jr. got into Yale.
  - Miss Hare, July; No. 3019
  - Hotel Villa Serbelloni to Miss Katharine G. Welling, 1927 July 21; No. 3020
    No one knows the sculptor of the statue. Thinks a sculptor could make a copy from pictures.
  - Mother to Miss Esther Hare, 1927 July 22; No. 3021
    Everyone away. Willing and I going to Bar Harbor and Willing going on to fish. Katharine will take charge of "Snatch". Getting skimmy produce from garden.
  - Truxtun to Mrs. H.B. Hare, 1927 July 23; No. 3022
    Am enjoying myself. Have two more weeks to go. Have been admitted to Yale.
  - Louise to Miss Esther Hare, 1927 July 23; No. 3023
    Sister-in-law died.
  - E. Bakhmeteff to Madamoiselle, 1927 July 24; No. 3024
  - Mother to Miss Esther Hare, 1927 July 24; No. 3025
    Enjoyed photos of baby and house and grounds. Truxtun saw Dempsey fight in New York. Going to Bar Harbor so we'll miss seeing K. and girls return. Truxtun's building. About Wood's daughter-in-law's death. Winston Churchill's book. George a very good servant.
  - Esther to Mrs. H.B. Hare, 1927 July 24; No. 3026
    Horace and I saw K. and the girls off. Had delightful two weeks at Beaufresne. Can't seem to get an earlier passage. Want to see Margaretta. Shopping. Engagements with friends and family.
  - Katharine to Miss Esther Hare, 1927 July 24; No. 3027
    Goodbye and thanks for wrap.
  - Mary Ogden to Miss Esther Hare, 1927 July 25; No. 3028
    So nice having you in Paris and hope you can come here. Clothes. Enjoyed Cornwall.
  - Horace to Mrs. Horace B. Hare, 1927 July 25; No. 3029
    Saw Katharine and children off. Delighted Truxtun is going to Yale. Visitors. Baby. Rainy weather.
  - Esther to Mrs. H.B. Hare, 1927 July 28; No. 3030
    Expect to sail August 3. Going to stay with Horace until I sail.
  - Miss Marian Powell to Miss Esther Hare, 1927 July 28; No. 3031
    About flowers and work.
  - T. Coulon, 1927 July 28; No. 3032
    Prescription.
  - Eugenia Cassatt to Mrs. Horace Binney Hare, 1927 July 29; No. 3033
    Did so enjoy your dinner. Of baby, Horace and Ellen. Mrs. Chew's death and Mrs. Biddle's son's illness.
  - Katharine to Miss Esther Hare, 1927 July 29; No. 3034
    Friendly letter. Bobby going to Harvard. Will you invite him for Christmas?
  - Willing to Esther Hare, 1927 July 29; No. 3035
    Telegram - arrived here on way to Bar Harbor.
  - N. to Miss E.B. Hare, 1927 July 29; No. 3036
    Travels - so sorry you are not joining us.
  - George to Esther Hare, 1927 July 30; No. 3037
    Telegram - sorry cannot come - chauffeur ill.
  - E. to Mrs. H.B. Hare, 1927 August 1; No. 3038
    Will join you at Bar Harbor after a few days at Radnor. Two wonderful days travel with H. and E. Baby adorable.
  - Mother to Miss Esther B. Hare, 1927 August 1; No. 3039
    General family news and of friends.
  - Miss Hare, 1927 August; No. 3040
    Bills - European trip.
  - The Pennsylvania Railroad to Mr. C.W. Hare, 1927 August 2; No. 3041
    Will meet your sister, Miss E.B. Hare, on her arrival at steamship pier.
  - Horace to Mrs. Horace B. Hare, 1927 August 2; No. 3042
    Visit to the coast. George Bakhmeteff postponed his visit. Thayers came. Will see Esther off. Baby, Katharine and Truxtun. Visitors - Miss Randolph, Arthur Meigs and Harry Brengle.
  - Willing to Mrs. Horace B. Hare, 1927 August 8; No. 3043
    Journey here. Companions, weather, etc.
  - Truxtun to Mrs. Horace B. Hare, 1927 August 8; No. 3044
    Family arrived home last week. On the new wing being built, weather and the family activities.
  - Mother to Miss Esther Hare, 1927 August 10; No. 3045
    About the house and servants. Willing left and I'm enjoying myself with friends.
  - Esther to Mrs. H.B. Hare, 1927 August 11; No. 3046
    Nearing home shores - comfortable voyage. Horace saw me off. Friends on board.
  - Mary F. Ogden to Miss Esther Hare, 1927 August 10; No. 3047
  - Mother to Miss Esther Hare, 1927 August 12; No. 3048
    Manager said you could bring "Snatch" if she did not bark.
  - Mother to Miss Esther Hare, 1927 August 12; No. 3049
    Gardiner Cassatt and I decided Horace and Ellen should come home earlier - Mrs. Cassatt has had two heart attacks. Very quiet here.
  - Cass to Mrs. Horace Binney Hare, 1927 August 13; No. 3050
    Suggestion you give Rosemary a jardiniere of pink geraniums. Social activities.
  - Willing to Mrs. Horace B. Hare, 1927 August 14; No. 3051
    Enjoying the fishing.
  - W.V.R. Abdill to Mrs. Hare, 1927 August 15; No. 3052
    Have copy of "The Life of Horace Binney" and letters for sale. (dealer in stamps, books, etc.)
  - Margaret Hanraltz to Miss Esther B. Hare, 1927 August 20; No. 3053
  - Wanamaker's and Strawbridges to Mrs. Horace B. Hare, 1927 August 22; No. 3054
  - Mary McIntyre to Miss Esther Hare, 1927 August 29; No. 3055
    Report on things at home.
  - Ellen Mary Hare to Miss Esther Hare, 1927 September 1; No. 3056
    Heard from Horace in Scotland - he will go to London, then back to Beaufresne and sail about September 10. Mother better. Ellen Mary is splendid - visited Eugenia's to see animals.
  - Ollie to Mrs. Emily P. Hare, 1927 September 15; No. 3057
    Thank you for package. Expect to spend winter in New England.
  - Adelaide and Grima to Miss Esther B. Hare, 1927 September 29; No. 3058
  - C.W. Beale to Mrs. Horace B. Hare, 1927 September 29; No. 3059
    Heartbroken over wife's illness.
  - C.W. Beale to Mrs. Horace B. Hare, 1927 October 6; No. 3060
    Thank you for your offer to send stimulant, but I can still get native product.
  - Cass to Mrs. Horace Binney Hare, 1927 October 10; No. 3061
    Postcards with information on the statue "Pan" and explanation of who Flossie is who sent them. Family news.
  - D. Hoffman to Mrs. Horace Binney Hare, 1927 October 14; No. 3062
    Thank you for invitation to Harford.
  - Carry Sinkler to Mrs. Horace Binney Hare, 1927 October 14; No. 3063
    Accepting invitation to visit you and help pour tea.
  - Hannah Chapman to Mrs. Horace Binney Hare, 1927 October 15; No. 3064
    Getting ready to close up here. How busy you will be introducing your first grandchild to "the gay world".
  - Walter Lowrie to Mrs. Horace Binney Hare, 1927 October 18; No. 3065
    In reply to your invitation for your "at home".
  - H.H. Battles (florist) to Mrs. Horace Binney Hare, 1927 October 18; No. 3066
    List of flowers sent for Katharine Jr. coming out party.
  - C.W. Beale to Mrs. Horace B. Hare, 1927 October 21; No. 3067
    Thank you for box of groceries. Maria improving.
  - Eugenia Cassatt to Mrs. Horace Binney Hare, 1927 October 22; No. 3068
    Thank you for flowers and box.
  - Jerome H. Knowles to Miss Constance R. Beale, 1927 October 25; No. 3069
    On sale of property at Cranberry Island.
  - Cass to Mrs. Hare, 1927 November 4; No. 3070
    Hurry, or the statue Pan may be sold. Friendly letter.
  - H.C. Mercer to Mrs. H.B. Hare, 1927 November 4; No. 3071
    On flowers, trees. Looking forward to your visit.
  - The Assemblies to Mrs. Horace Binney Hare, 1927 November 6; No. 3072
    Enclosing form for subscription.
  - O.P. Smith to Mrs. Emily P. Hare, 1927 November 14; No. 3073
    Pleasant staying with you. Hope your eye is better.
  - Cass to Mrs. Hare, 1927 November 17; No. 3074
    About your eyes and my shin.
  - Ollie to Mrs. H.B. Hare, 1927 November 25; No. 3075
    Thank you for Thanksgiving present. Want to get away from here - can't find work. Tell family not to ask unworthy people about me - it makes trouble.
  - Giorge B. Armenio to Mrs. H.B. Hare, 1927 November 29; No. 3076
    Now working at Mrs. Cassatt's. Announcing engagement and would like you to come.
  - O.P. Smith to Mrs. H.B. Hare, 1927 December 3; No. 3077
    Thank you for inviting me to spend the night. Want to go to New England where I am sure I could find work with skiing.
  - Neil and Mrs. Coyle to Miss Esther Hare, 1927 December 9; No. 3078
    Friendly letter (inquiring about everyone).
  - Barbara and Walter Lowrie to Mrs. Horace Binney Hare, 1927 December 11; No. 3079
    Christmas card (picture of home by the sea).
  - Marie C. Peterson to Mrs. H.B. Hare, 1927 December 23; No. 3080
  - C.W. Beale to Mrs. Horace B. Hare, 1927 December 30; No. 3081
    Had our usual Christmas party. Wife better.
  - Cass to Mrs. Hare, 1927 December 31; No. 3082
    Thank you for lovely lace pillow.
  - Label, 1928; No. 3083
    A. De Luze & Fils, Bordeaux - Graves Superiour
  - Esther B. Hare, 1928; No. 3084
    Engagement calendar.
  - Cass to Mrs. Hare, 1928 January 17; No. 3085
    Invitation to an "At Home".
  - Ollie to Mrs. H.B. Hare, 1928 February 6; No. 3086
    Expecting wire from you when you come.
  - Bank of N.A. & Trust Co. to Mrs. Emily P. Hare, 1928 February 7; No. 3087
    Request you deposit check - (notation, never received).
  - Bank of N.A. & Trust Co. to Mrs. Emily P. Hare, 1928 February 14; No. 3088
    Sending duplicate check.
  - Horace to Mrs. Horace Binney Hare, 1928 February 27; No. 3089
    Arrived and went to Mrs. Cassatt's for breakfast. Looking for nursemaid. Willing going to Hot Springs.
  - Mrs. Donohue to Miss Esther Hare, 1928 March 6; No. 3090
    Returning to America in May.
  - Katharine to Mrs. Horace Binney Hare, 1928 March 6; No. 3091
    General family correspondence.
  - Carry to Mrs. Horace Binney Hare, 1928 March 7; No. 3092
    Miss seeing you and looking forward to being with you in Spring.
  - St. David's Church to Mr. Hare, 1928 March 7; No. 3093
    Letter in regard to grave stones, and deeds to plots - C. Willing, T. Truxtun, Horace B., and Esther B. Hare.
  - Robert Hare to Mrs. Horace B. Hare, 1928 March 12; No. 3094
    About Mother's birthday. Princeton and Penn basketball game. I have decided to go to St. Mark's.
  - Truxtun to Mrs. Horace B. Hare, 1928 March 12; No. 3095
    Heavy snow. Horace and Ellen dined here for a surprise birthday party for Katharine. Saw "She Stoops to Conquer", and Penn and Princeton basketball game.
  - Ellen Coyle to Miss Esther B. Hare, 1928 March 21; No. 3096
    Thank you for gifts on ship.
  - C.W. Beale to Mrs. Horace B. Hare, 1928 March 23; No. 3097
    Distressed to hear you have never recovered from your fall. Colored peoples knowledge and Voodooism. Congratulate Horace on new baby.
  - Ollie to Willing Hare, 1928 May 1; No. 3098
    Thank you for clothes. Baby burned and other boys have measles. In regard to stored furniture. Started working.
  - Ollie to Mrs. H.B. Hare, 1928 May 15; No. 3099
    Thank you for lovely things.
  - Ollie to Mrs. H.B. Hare, 1928 June 15; No. 3100
    Thank you for generous present. School commencement. Visited Aunt Connie.
  - Dr. T.F. Branson to Miss Esther B. Hare, 1928 March 26; No. 3100a
    Excuse from jury duty.
  - Newspaper article - Public Ledger, 1928 May 13; No. 3100b
    Pictures and news item on Radnor Race.
  - Truxtun to Mrs. Horace B. Hare, 1928 June 17; No. 3101
    Very pleasant trip and companions on board ship.
  - O.P. Smith to Mrs. H.B. Hare, 1928 June 21; No. 3102
    Disappointed I could not come, but I had to work.
  - Arthur Meigs to Mrs. Horace B. Hare, 1928 June 22; No. 3103
    Appreciate your going to dedication.
  - Truxtun to Mrs. H.B. Hare, 1928 June 26; No. 3104
    Travel and sights.
  - Katharine Storm to Mrs. H.B. Hare, 1928 June 26; No. 3105
    Order blank for binders and abdominal supporters.
  - K.G.W. (Cass) to Mrs. Hare, 1928 June 26; No. 3106
    Enjoyed being at Harford. Friendly letter.
  - Viola to Mrs. Horace B. Hare, 1928 June 28; No. 3107
    Thank you for dress for birthday.
  - Cass to Mrs. Horace Binney Hare, 1928 July 1; No. 3108
    Find I can go to Italy next winter - won't you and Esther go with me. Going to Cragsmoor. Read "Rivalry" by Mrs. Schuyler. Poem - "Exteriors".
  - E.F.B. to Emily, 1928 July 2; No. 3109
    Looking forward to seeing you on the 4th.
  - M. Bayard to Mrs. Hare, 1928 July 4; No. 3110
  - Truxtun (nephew) to C. Willing Hare, 1928 July 4; No. 3111
    Sights and travels. (postcards)
  - T.H. Stevenson to Mrs. Horace Binney Hare, 1928 July 19; No. 3112
    Insurance policy on three portraits in studio.
  - Fidelity-Philadelphia Trust Company to Mrs. Emily P. Hare, 1928 July 23; No. 3113
    Mortgage papers on 254 S. 21st St.
  - E.F.B. to Mrs. Horace B. Hare, 1928 July 31; No. 3114
    Praising your love and attention to Mother. Family news.
  - Truxtun to Mrs. Horace B. Hare, 1928 August 2; No. 3115
    Losing interest in other things - living routinely. Aunt Maria ill. Truxtun arrived home - had most satisfactory trip - upset now by Cottrell's death. My Italian purchases have arrived - gates are good looking.
  - Ellen MacVeagh to Miss Esther Hare, 1928 August 3; No. 3116
    Thank you for taking care of Margaretta's request - sending basket for Virginia. Snapshot of Virginia MacVeagh.
  - Willing to Mrs. Horace Binney Hare, 1928 August 12; No. 3117
    Description of ship, passengers and voyage to Europe.
  - E.F.B. to Emily, 1928 August 13; No. 3118
    Unfortunate trip to Northeast Harbor - Maria got worse and we had to return home.
  - Newspaper article - The Times, 1928 August 15; No. 3119
    Mr. Hoover and Mr. Smith - candidates for the presidency.
  - Willing to Mrs. Horace B. Hare, 1928 August 20; No. 3120
    Description of motor trip and memories of other trips. Travel plans.
  - Mother to C. Willing Hare, 1928 August 2; No. 3120a
    Bon voyage note, and requesting you "become a man" instead of just "drifting" ("come back as you used to be").
  - Mother to C. Willing Hare, 1928 August 9; No. 3120b
    Bathing in salt water. Social engagements.
  - Horace to Mr. C. Willing Hare, 1928 August 9; No. 3120c
    In reference to work being done on house (Harford).
  - Leonard T. Beale to Mrs. Horace B. Hare, 1928 August 21; No. 3121
    Doctors say Mrs. Beale doing as well as can be expected.
  - Dr. Albert Stengel to Mrs. Horace B. Hare, 1928 August 21; No. 3122
    In reference to Mrs. Beale's illness.
  - Edward F. Beale to Mrs. Horace Binney Hare, 1928 August 24; No. 3123
    Maria improving but fear return of condition.
  - The Pennsylvania Company to Mrs. H.B. Hare, 1928 August 29; No. 3124
    In reference to securities held under will of Charles Willing.
  - Maria to Mrs. H.B. Hare, 1928 August 29; No. 3125
    Thank you for tray. Have been very sick.
  - Celia Richmond to Miss Esther Hare, 1928 September 5; No. 3126
    Sending white scarf to you at Miss Chew's request.
  - C. Willing Hare, 1928 September 6; No. 3127
    On board S.S. "New York" - Dinner menu.
  - Garden Club of Philadelphia, 1928 September; No. 3128
    List of autumn meetings.
  - Horace to Mrs. Horace B. Hare, 1928 September 13; No. 3129
    Saw Willing - trip did him good. They are still worried about Aunt Maria, but she is better. Truxtun, Jr. may come to you with Willing. Overseeing the work being done at Harford.